{
    "subject": "resource/Nardin_Academy",
    "predicate": "property/accreditation",
    "object": "resource/Middle_States_Association_of_Colleges_and_Schools",
    "human_readable": "Nardin Academy is accredited by Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9599472880363464,
            "question": "By which association is Nardin Academy accredited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9465088844299316,
            "question": "Is Nardin Academy accredited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7651317119598389,
            "question": "What type of institution is Nardin Academy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7280355095863342,
            "question": "What does the Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools accredit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6629399061203003,
            "question": "What organization accredits Nardin Academy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5636797547340393,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other institutions accredited by the Middle States Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5108692049980164,
            "question": "What standards must Nardin Academy meet to maintain its accreditation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1689567118883133,
            "question": "What are some benefits of attending an accredited school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12051641941070557,
            "question": "What is the significance of accreditation for educational institutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04210402071475983,
            "question": "How does accreditation ensure quality education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nardin Academy is accredited by Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7842_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of accreditation for educational institutions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7842_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some benefits of attending an accredited school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7842_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What standards must Nardin Academy meet to maintain its accreditation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7842_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7842_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7842/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt, Nardin Academy is indeed accredited by the Middle States Accreditation Board."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"Nardin Academy is accredited by the Middle States Accreditation Board,\" which supports the triple stating that Nardin Academy is accredited by the Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (note that the Middle States Accreditation Board and Middle States Association of Schools and Colleges are one entity)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}